# **JAMES**

## Senior Shopify Engineer

### CONTACT

mju34170@gmail.com

https://github.com/Monster-0117 🧻

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Computer Science Kyoto University May 2014 - April 2018 Kyoto, JP

### **SKILLS**

JavaScript (ES6, React, Redux, Node.js, VUE, Angular)
Python (Django)
SQL (SQLite, MySQL)
Cloud (GCP, AWS)
Typescript
HTML/ CSS
CSS Framework(Bootstrap,
Tailwind CSS, Materialize CSS..)
Shopify
PHP(Laravel, CI)
MongoDB

### **ABOUT ME**

Hi, there. I am a Senior Shopify Engineer with over 8 years of experience. First of all, I have rich experience in frontend including CSS and JavaScript frameworks React and Vue. At several companies, I have created unique site and received good reviews from customers. I also developed many ecommerce sites using Shopify. In the meantime, I participated in the project that was developed SEO and mobile-friendly. Customer satisfaction and time compliance is my policy. I am sure that you will find my work satisfactory. Thanks.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **Shopify Engineer**

### **MEDINAUTEN GMBH**

July 2019 - January 2020 / Munich, Germany

- developed several e-commerce sites
- Developed SEO and mobile-friendly sites that rank high on search engines.
- It uses Shopify APIs to integrate with other systems.

### AHT TECH ISC

September 2020 - April 2021 / Kawasaki, Japan

- By developing and using a unique theme for the company itself, the ecommerce site receives more than 4,000 customers per day than ever before
- Create a payment gateway as the third party integration

### Frontend Engineer

#### **PAYPAY**

January 2015 - August 2016 / Minato City, Tokyo, Japan

- developed and maintained e-commerce web applications using TypeScript and React.js.
- Mentored 3 junior front end developers on the team
- Developed the company's own CSS framework

#### **IUSTWATCH**

May 2017 - February 2018 / Berlin, Germany

- Designing customer-oriented sites, they averaged over 15,000 customers per day.
- Customize React Bootstrap theming.
- Maintained and improved the client portal React application
- By using React and Redux, the site loading speed was increased by 20%